Hey guys, welcome to another video, so in this video I will be going to explain one of
the often important topics to dump a registry, I was using the salmon system high, basically
what is the salmon system, so salmon is like security account managers, so all the user
credentials will be saved on the database, okay, so often the protectors view, so one of
the command to dump the salmon system high, and they will be crack using various tools,
okay, I will show you how to do that, so let me, it's pretty simple to do that, okay,
so I will put it as an administrator, before that let me do one thing, let me, I have
dumped previously, I will delete both of the things and I will show how to dump that,
okay, so in overall this salmon system high contain the credentials, it's like a credential
database, okay, all the credentials to be saved are there, so if you need, you can find
it from the refrigerator, let's move to the local machine, and here you can find a salmon,
and a system, you are going to dump both of the registry keys, okay, so if you click on
here there is nothing, but actually there is a lot of things will be saved, okay, so let
me show how to dump that rich, save, let's scale them, so salmon, so you have to give the
directory, okay, so now we can see the command has
completed, so let me move on to the, yeah, so here you can find the directory, so the
next one we are going to dump the system, oh, sorry, now we have both of the highest
sitting under the target directory, so this both of the files contain, it's like credential
database, okay, we will be seeing the registry as a database, so the credentials will be
saved on that database, so if you can be able to crack both of the file, you can easily
find out what a credential has been stored there, so from that you can get the credentials,
okay, so let me pull both of the files into my calling machine, so you can use different
methods, so probably we'll be using the command and control, right, that call it terminal
command and control, so once you install a malware or a mobile software or you'll be getting
a console there and you'll be using that, so just pull both of the files there, okay,
let me close this video and we'll be connecting you in the next video to crack both of
this file, okay, so see you guys, bye bye.